

### Curriculum Vitae of: Ann F. DeRose, CPA

# General Background

Since 2001, Ms. DeRose has focused her career entirely on investigative auditing and the measurement of damages. She has diversified experience in matters dealing with loss of earnings, third party liability, stock/inventory losses, fidelity losses, and personal injury.

#### Education

# **Bachelor of Business Administration - 1980**

Summa Cum Laude

University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire, Eau Claire, Wisconsin

## **Subsequent Accounting Courses – 2004-2005**

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, Milwaukee, Wisconsin Carroll College, Waukesha, Wisconsin

# **Professional Status**

- \*Certified Public Accountant in Wisconsin since 2007
- \*Member, Wisconsin Institute of Certified Public Accountants
- \*Member, American Institute of Certified Public Accountants

# **Professional History**

**Insight Forensic Accountants, S.C. (formerly Peters & Associates),** New Berlin, WI, 2000 to present Staff Accountant

Susan G. Betsworth, CPA, LeMars, IA, 1996 to 1999

**Accounting Assistant** 

#### First Wisconsin National Bank of Madison, Madison, WI, 1983 to 1992

Assistant Vice President – positions included Branch Administration Coordinator, Branch Manager, Information Services Manager, Loan Accounting Manager, and Systems Analyst.

**A.B. Dick Company**, Madison, WI, 1981 to 1983

Marketing Support Representative

In her current position at Insight Forensic Accountants, Ms. DeRose is responsible for the evaluation of a variety of damages. Ms. DeRose has experience in the review of insurance claims for economic and physical damages in a variety of businesses and industries. She also provides litigation support services. Specific assignments include work in the following areas:

\*Loss of Income/Business Income Losses

\*Extra Expense Measurement

\*Employee Dishonesty Losses

\*Theft Losses

\*Personal Injury/Wrongful Death Damages

\*Economic Damages

\*Inventory Losses

\*Product Liability/Product Recall Losses